~~
I really liked the fireworks.
That really made me cry anytime.
~~
The Veggies.
What?
We're eating fried chicken.
Of course!
Thank you very much.
You got the car all ready to go.
You know, coming from a Korean...
They don't understand how spicy kimchi is.
Can I try some of that?
Yes.
Is it okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to go back to Korea.
Don't look at it yet.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Two.
Three.
Who the hell are you calling?
I was wrong. It's Vegeta.
It's Vegeta.
I said it's Vegeta.
Vegeta here.
What did you think of the name Vegeta?
How'd he do with a name like that?
He says he's one of three celebrities he likes.
He's a fan.
Where are you going now?
I'm going to Ryuji's talk event.
Have fun.
It looks like we're done.
Thank you for watching!
It's been a long stillor...
When is it coming on?
What?
When does it go on the air?
When are we on the air?
It just came on live.
It's on YouTube.
It's not "Watch Your Shoulders.
When we're together.
You want to take a picture of this today?
Can we both ride?
Can I take a picture of you with him?
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Okay, thank you very much.
He's been banging his glove the whole time.
I'm not a punching machine.
You can't keep touching my glove.
Don't touch my glove.
What the hell?
I'm not lost.
Lost?
You look like a stray.
50 years?
It's Vegeta.
Are you okay?
I didn't get separated from my parents.
Here?
Over there.
This popular?
The luge stage?
So many Earthlings.
What's going on?
Don't get too close, okay?
It's a tail.
That's not a tail.
It's Vegeta.
That's Ultra Seven.
I'm gonna sit down.
Ryuju stage.
It's Vegeta.
Ryuju Stage
I'm gonna sit down.
Don't sit down.
It's Kasi.
Really?
Both of you.
Thank you very much.
You happy now?
He's only seven months old.
He's so quiet.
Sorry. Sorry.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
He's cool.
Combat value.
I was about a 3.
I'm Ryuji, the cook's sister.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Hi, I'm Shunsuke Inada.
Pleased to meet you.
For this project, Mr. Inada and I have come up with a recipe for eating Fukuoka rice flour at home, and we're going to take turns introducing it.
It's like a cooking talk show where we take turns introducing the recipes.
The main ingredient used this time is rice flour!
I use this rice flour and Hakata Ichiban Chicken.
Do you all know about this? Hakata Ichiban Chicken
Hakata Ichiban Chicken is also used in the food stall I'm setting up today.
Mochikochiki
This is it!
You can eat it at a food stall.
You can eat it at a yatai, but
I'm sure there are some of you who would like to know how to make it.
So today, I'd like to demonstrate how to make
I'd like to demonstrate how to make this Mochikochiki.
Thank you very much.
Let's put in the seasonings.
First of all, grated ginger.
Grated ginger.
I'll mix it a little more in the bat.
Grated ginger, grated garlic.
Double use garlic and ginger.
And soy sauce is the key to taste.
Soy sauce is the standard for spicy food.
This is honey.
I put honey in it.
Many people don't fry food at home.
Yes, many people do.
But I don't want to fry food at home.
I don't want to eat freshly fried food.
Freshly fried.
That's the goal, isn't it?
I'm a big proponent of deep frying at home.
Because it uses the most oil.
So I think home fried food is not so bad.
I really understand.
Do you know anyone who says they don't fry food at home?
There are many people who are interested in cooking.
I think that's because many people are interested in cooking, and I think that they are watching me and Mr. Inada.
Do you have my side of the esaijeness?
Thank you very much.
The devil's recipe.
It's a recipe that I took care of.
Thank you very much.
It's not too hard.
There are a lot of fried foods.
I think you've been doing it.
It contains honey, so it can burn easily.
It tends to burn easily.
So, if you use too high a heat
If you cook it over a high flame, it will get burnt.
I think it's better to fry them slowly over medium heat.
I think it's better to fry them slowly.
I think you'll get a nice color right away.
I think it's easier to fry them at home if you think you can fry them with this amount of oil.
If you fry them in a lot of oil, they are very tasty.
Here is the completion of my Mochiko Chicken made with rice flour.
Today, I would like to introduce you to this person.
I don't mind if I eat it.
I'd like this person to eat it.
Please do.
Hey, you guys!
It's Vegeta.
I hear you're making some kind of a mess.
Today, Master Vegeta here
He's going to take your food.
You'll be pleased.
I'm counting on you.
Freshly fried.
Thank you for watching.
Which way are you coming? You don't have chopsticks.
Trial man! I have them! Trial man! Trial man!
Ah, here, here, here... you, a bedouin...
Veggie Southern? You eat fried chicken? Of course I do.
Thank you very much. It's Bulma's specialty.
I didn't know. Let's have some.
Freshly fried.
Just fried.
The inside is so soft and chewy.
It's so sticky.
Of course, it's crispy around the edges.
Very juicy.
It's coated with honey.
Honey is a barrier.
It's a barrier.
It's better than my first bite.
Better than an alien's arm.
I had it in book 17.
And the meat is well-seasoned, too.
It's already well-seasoned.
Once you try this, you'll never eat any other fried chicken.
It's like a bird's
The Final Flush.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the final flush.
~~
Oh, good, then. To the fried food store.
I said too much.
Yes, sir.
~~
To the dance.
What?
Your pockets are popped.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I made a mistake.
Sign.
Sign
Sign here.
Where is it?
This one's better, right?
Right here.
I'll sign here.
November 5th.
What is your name?
Nao.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Shake hands.
Thank you.
We have the same name.
We have the same name, Ryuji.
You're Ryuji?
It's difficult, difficult.
Thank you very much.
Welcome.
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you're being so honest.
I'm very happy.
I'm sorry, I didn't bring any books.
Not at all.
Thank you for all your help.
I have to go buy some fried chicken.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thank you
Saab is the best
Thank you very much.
That's a lot of messages.
That's hot.
That's great.
I'm usually born from your books.
I'm born in Ryuji's books.
Everyday.
Youtube and books
At least once a day.
I watch Mr. Ryuji at least once a day.
I might be watching as much as my husband
as much as my husband.
I like the supreme fried rice the best.
Delicious.
Say it again.
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious?
Yummy.
I don't cook for myself.
I don't cook by myself, but I've been served a simple dish called "Chicken Ramen".
It's great.
It's great. Even if you don't cook like me.
You can do it!
What?
It won't disappear.
That's great.
I got this from Sun.
40-second wait.
Hello?
I didn't realize it was that busy.
I felt like I was taking pictures all the time.
But it was fun.
Thank you very much.
There's a lot of great drinks here.
Hello, everyone.
First of all, I'd like to explain why this stage was chosen.
A staff member said to me.
I told the staff that there is a Korean YouTube star who is very similar to me.
I was introduced to her and told her that I would like to do a talk show with her.
But...
Is she like me? Do I look like her? I mean, the vibe...
Riko's fans might wonder why.
But the staff told me.
And this Vegeta-san...
Yes, Vegeta-san said that too.
He said, "You really look like him.
I can't wait to meet him.
What do you think?
I'm glad to hear that I look like such a cute idol.
Thank you very much.
This year, too. Seo-an-chan is a year older than me.
That's right.
I'd like to talk about various things today.
I'd like to talk about a few things.
I think...
Korean people like spicy food, don't they?
Yes, they do.
Do you like it enough?
I'm not so good with spicy food even among Koreans.
I'm not so good with spicy food.
But I've learned from my conversation with the staff.
Japanese people are not used to spicy food as much as Koreans think
Japanese people are not so accustomed to spicy food than Koreans think.
From a Korean point of view, they don't understand how spicy kimchi is.
Kimchi is spicy.
Is there an excuse? It's spicy.
Spicy. Is that so? Here's Menbei's spicy version.
I happened to be in an izakaya in Osaka, and the customer next to me from Osaka happened to be back from a trip to Fukuoka that day, and he bought a quantity of this.
The customer next to me in Osaka happened to be back from a trip to Fukuoka that day, and he bought a quantity of this.
I tried the plain flavor, but I haven't had it yet, so I'd like to try it. Menshiko? Like mentaiko crackers. Wow.
Menbei dry. Have you ever had it?
So-so, so-so, so-so. If you say so-so, so-so, so-so in Japan, maybe...
Yes.
It's delicious. It's not spicy, but...
It's delicious.
It's not spicy? So the plain one wasn't spicy either? When I ate it.
It tastes different than the plain one.
It tastes different, not really.
Is it spicy? Is it spicy? Everyone is.
I think it has a bit of an aftertaste.
Oh, the chili?
Oh, yes.
Chili pepper cod roe?
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yum.
Oh, good.
I'm glad it's good.
Delicious!
Fukuoka has a lot of good food.
That's right. Delicious food.
This is my third trip to Fukuoka.
Is it spicy?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You look more surprised than usual.
Is that so?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Have a drink.
Thank you very much.
It was a great time. Thanks to all of you.
Thank you for watching.
Bye-bye.
It was a lot of fun.
Well, it's finally now.
I really didn't realize how short the hour was.
I'm dying of numbness!
Thank you for your hard work.
You couldn't handle it at all, could you?
I hope you're all right.
If I'd left him alone, he'd have talked forever.
It's such an easy project, isn't it?
That's great.
It was super fun.
You were so easy to talk to.
You really pulled me along.
Even more so.
It was a fun time.
Let's do it again when we can.
I really look forward to working with you again.
I'm so busy
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
I can't believe how short the hour was.
I thought it was over.
I thought it was a shame to end it.
I'm sure we can do it again in the next project, even if it's just the two of us talking.
I closed the show.
I had a guest today.
It was a little bit awkward.
You were very considerate.
Very considerate.
You're super smart.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. We talked about the same amount.
It was really nice.
I see.
Thanks to you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Can I eat that?
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
This is what I was drinking.
I can totally hear you.
It tastes like it.
Mm.
Wow.
Hold on a second.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's hard. Can you see it? This is the camera.
Almost there. Time to go.
But it's delicious.
I haven't had it in Korea for a long time.
In Japan? Since I came to Japan.
I've never had it in Japan.
Ohhhhhh!
Boo-boo!
My dad's idol did it too, and it was kind of a fad, but now I think it's back.
Basically, it's an atmosphere that doesn't close as it should.
me
I came to the fireworks show today.
Oh, you want to watch from this position?
Yes, that's right.
After three days of the show, it's finally like fireworks for the first place game.
Yes, sir.
How was the three days?
It was fun.
I was so happy to see so many Japanese people unexpectedly at my booth.
I don't want to go back to Korea.
I'm going to have fun.
I will have fun!
I'll have fun!
I also have a child who is just like me
We're all in this together
Good luck, funny customer!
Customer: It's 100 yen!
Customer: I say "bro" all at once
Customer: Say "brother" all at once
Customer: Good morning.
Customer: Yes, sir.
Customer: It's delicious!
Customer: How is it?
Customer: What is that?
Customer: Two more
Customer: 400 yen, please.
Customer: I'll have a set.
Thank you for watching.
I heard that even though they came till night, they probably used up most of the hot water they brought with them, so I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that.
Can you see it at this point?
I can see it!
Okay, let's see what we can do.
Okay, first one.
Let's see,
Mr. Diamant, let's turn around and walk.
Over there? Over here?
Don't look over there.
There's a lemon booth for you.
Now,
Over there.
Don't look yet.
Wow, there's a lot of people here.
Can I take a picture?
What's that?
I'm going to walk around with my eyes closed so I don't see them.
It's kind of sad.
I'm excited.
I haven't seen it yet.
I haven't looked.
Is Lil' Mew still straight?
Have you seen it? Has Lil' Mu seen it?
Yes, sir.
Look at the relay officer.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Here you go.
Oh, my God.
It's so cute.
At first...
When I saw it yesterday, it was all white.
But now there are so many pictures.
So cute!
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
So cute!
Amazing!
I just painted this.
Oh, my God.
What are you drawing?
That's great.
Everyone's so good at drawing.
So colorful.
It's hard to believe this was all white.
That's amazing.
Beautiful.
Yesterday, we used paints.
You know...
Here.
You painted a picture of garbage.
It's beautiful.
I asked him to paint it with beautiful colors.
The staff says that there are 20 or 30 layers.
There are about 20 or 30 layers.
Is that right?
He really painted on the paint all the way through.
Yesterday
It looked like this.
And today...
Posca.
I painted a jellyfish
Or a whale.
I think it's a human hand or something.
That's right.
I thought it was a star.
But it's a hand.
Yes.
I can't even begin to count.
Sea creatures.
Such wonderful colors.
If you put the colors on top of each other
something more
I don't know.
I thought it would be muddy.
That's the image I had.
Wow, it's so cheap!
It's so beautiful.
Yes, it is.
How many people painted this picture?
painted this picture?
I don't know how many.
Too many to count.
I've lost count.
I'm sure there are at least a hundred people.
That's a lot.
A hundred, three hundred?
That's what you said.
Oh, my God.
That's a lot of people.
You're still drawing them, aren't you?
Myu...
How many people did you draw?
I found it...
I drew the heart in the upper left corner.
That kind of heart?
And then someone drew a border around it.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
They framed it.
It's a great collaboration.
I'm glad I can be prettier.
What about you, Myu-chan?
You just drew the blue heart next to the blue heart on the top?
Yes, that's right.
And I don't know if it's there now.
I don't know if it's there now, but I drew a star and some other things.
That's nice.
I'm glad.
Do you want me to draw you too?
Sure, go ahead.
Please do.
Tosika.
Green
What should I draw?
Squid?
That's good.
Let's draw it. I'll draw it with you.
I think he'll draw a squid.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'll draw.
Nature
I'll draw my favorite sweet potato.
You know potatoes?
Imo!
Can you draw me a potato? Thank you!
He's tracing it for me!
Thank you!
Draw a potato here.
He traced it for me.
Thank you!
That's great!
Moo-moo-moo.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Thank you!
You're so good.
Irmiyu is on location for a children's book.
You know what I've been doing?
Yes, I have.
We can make recycled paper out of plastic bottle fibers.
Recycled paper is made from plastic bottles.
To see how it's made.
To see how it's done.
I also went with a student
and Lisa Minatogawa Kara Rhythm
and Lisa Minatogawa Colorism, a student
the story of the picture book.
That's great!
I'm off to the factory where we make our paper
I'm going there.
What's that?
Oh, my God!
It's big.
Touch it.
It's so soft.
Like a person.
A background of plastic bottles.
Even if you've never seen it before.
It's easy to understand.
The paper for the picture book
from plastic bottles
paper from plastic bottles.
I hope it will inspire people to recycle.
I thought it would be nice if people would recycle.
I thought of something like this.
Will you make it with me again?
Yes! I'd be very happy to work with you!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
I often see the sea in picture book stories
I would like to use it as a picture
I plan to cut out a part of the picture
I plan to cut out a part of the picture and make use of it.
The production of the picture book
Goo Goo Channel will continue to
We may be able to report
Enjoy!
Fun!
It's fun!
Let's do it!
Tea Rain Christmas
I want to do this one too!
You've been doing a great job of keeping track.
Sign here!
I need someone to run for it.
I want it!
I'm going to make the paint fly.
The more you skip it, the better.
Easy to use
Easier to use as material
It makes it more personal
I'll skip it.
Are you going to fly with me?
Yes! I'll do my best!
Put it directly on your hand.
Everybody, take the middle one.
Go for it! Not too close to the edge.
One brake and you're off the top.
We'll go down from the top.
Sit on the bottom.
Good for you.
Last hit.
How'd you like that?
Perfect.
Perfect?
I have to admit that it's a little easier to use as material.
I don't think you would use this as a fish in a picture book, for example.
That's why I skipped the white a little bit.
By making it a little blurry
I decided to make it easier to use as a material by making it a little blurred.
Was there any picture that caught your attention?
A picture that caught your eye?
When I was there, a mother was drawing a picture of a blowfish.
A child asked her mother to draw it.
And then an adult would draw it.
And the kids were happy to see them.
It's normal for children to draw, but to see an adult doing it, I thought it was wonderful.
I thought it was wonderful.
Penguins are very good, aren't they?
Very good.
Even though it's a silhouette.
It's easy to recognize.
It's a solid color, so maybe...
Maybe.
I think it makes it stand out.
That makes sense.
I thought it was a star, but it was a crowd of people.
I think the work has a lot of energy.
If you stare at the store. If you stare at the store inside the store,
I enjoy eating food when I gaze at the store.
When I look at the store, I enjoy eating the food.
We now gaze at the stores.
First we went to these stores.
Thank you for watching.
Yes, ma'am.
In.
If you say so fans than the fireworks are good, I don't have it backwards. And if you go out in front of it and say what you think of it, you're already in a situation where you can't
I'm sure everyone can watch that exchange.
That's the way to do it, please.
Let's see what you think.
Let's have him come out.
The audience applauded.
Thank you very much.
Three, two, one.
Okay, so...
And now for the finale.
Fireworks Challenge Corner
Nice fireworks
It's getting cooler
It's dark
After this
7:00 p.m.
The oldest fireworks display...
Actually, we're going to set off the fireworks at the beginning of the show.
We produced the fireworks
We produced the fireworks at the beginning of the show.
What kind of fireworks are we going to produce?
I'm not sure if you've seen the video.
I wonder if any of you have seen our video.
on the Goo Goo channel.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you the short version.
We are Batten Shoujo-tai and our song is called
It's called "Kono Minato".
We have a song called "Kono Minato".
And we're going to show fireworks to the tune of the song.
will be shot off to the tune of the song.
In the middle of the fireworks
R Fujimoto, and Batten Shoujo-tai
Ai Kiyama, and I, Riko Ueda
actually made the fireworks
fireworks that I made by myself
will be launched today.
I really don't know what will happen.
I'm so excited!
It's already pretty easy to understand
I'm sure you'll be able to get them up.
Well, well, well...
Yes, that's right.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be mute for the song or not.
I don't know, I don't know...
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know, I don't know.
Well, if it's really a dirty firework...
If it's really dirty fireworks, you can just assume it's us.
Even if it's a little bit ugly.
I'd appreciate it if you could applaud.
I'd be happy.
The original fireworks.
I'll wear a batten.
Riko is the red button
Fujimoto-san's is a few body pillars.
Please try to find them!
I don't know if it will really work.
Besides, you know...
In case you're wondering...
The order in which the fireworks will be launched in this port is...
I, Riko Ueda's fireworks
followed by Ai-chan's fireworks
And just before the last chorus
right before the last chorus, which is called the last chorus.
Fujimoto-san's several body pillars
It's a bit of a big responsibility
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, I hope you enjoy it.
I'm sure the fireworks will be beautiful.
That's all I'm saying.
Now let's see what we can do to produce them.
The students helped us produce them.
Are there any students here?
Please come out.
I'm out now, please.
Thank you for coming out so late.
They came up with the idea of fireworks with us.
Well, since we're here... one at a time.
Hey, state of mind.
What do you think?
Oh...
Well...
I've never designed fireworks before in my life.
I've never done it before in my life.
I was at a loss at first.
But as I was working with you all
I got more and more ideas.
I think we came up with a good design.
I hope you'll take a look.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Well, we've never done anything like this before.
We've worked very hard on it.
We're looking forward to seeing what kind of fireworks it's going to be.
Thank you very much.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm the only one who doesn't know what they look like yet.
I don't know.
It's so nice of you to come.
I have the flu.
I've got the flu.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope it's going to be beautiful.
That's all that matters.
Thank you very much.
We worked really hard on the lyrics and the design of the fireworks.
We're looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
We asked Mr. Izumi, the fireworks designer
We asked Mr. Izumi, the pyrotechnician, to produce as much as feasible.
You threw everything you had into it, didn't you?
That's not a good way to put it.
I asked him to think about it.
So I said, "How about you think about it?
I'm Mr. Izumi, a pyrotechnician from Makino Art Factory.
I'm Izumi, a pyrotechnician at Makino Art Factory.
It's like we're going to shoot off fireworks.
It's nice... and dependable.
He's so cool.
Nice to meet you.
Keena, you haven't arrived yet.
She's still working as an MC?
Keena!
Keena.
Great timing!
Just in time for the fireworks.
Just in time.
Good morning. - Good morning.
I'm home.
The festival just finished.
I'm sure many visitors will be moving here from the other side.
I think they're moving this way one after another.
They are so far back!
Fireworks this time, with everyone's name "Minato Kono",
We are going to shoot off fireworks with your song "Kono Minato" and the songs of the artists who performed at the festival today,
The fireworks will be set off in a completely programmed manner,
The most important thing is that the PA, sound engineer and pyrotechnicians work well together.
I see, so they are in different locations.
I see.
I'm nervous.
Where is the PA?
Behind?
Side, front?
Uh, behind, uh, yeah, over there.
Oh, so you can't see the fireworks.
That's sad.
It's heavy and there's a wall behind it.
But if you make noise, you can come back.
You're that irresponsible.
Hurry, hurry.
I hope you can see it in the delivery.
So, the pyrotechnicians are on the hill behind you.
The hill?
It's a distance.
Where are you going?
I see.
Let's check it out.
Yes, let's just... yes, let's get ready.
Wow.
Daisuke-san, Daisuke-san.
Daisuke-san.
Can you get through?
Here you go.
Are you ready?
Yes, Jumilla is ready.
No, it's not.
Great.
Where's Mr. Vegeta?
Mr. Vegeta?
You can't see him today.
Vegeta, you shouldn't do that, he'll say you're dirty.
Gently.
You shouldn't do that.
About five years ago, I went to a fireworks show,
I want you to write "No dirty fireworks" in the script.
I knew that the pyrotechnicians wouldn't want to be told that.
Yes, we want beautiful fireworks.
What did you say at that time?
I said, "You're going to do it! It was ambiguous.
Freeza was fine with it.
"Beautiful fireworks!" Frieza says, "It's a beautiful firework!
Vegeta is in trouble.
He has a bad mouth.
I'm glad you're not here today.
He's back today, too.
One minute left?
One more minute!
I can't wait!
Almost time.
We're looking forward to the fireworks, aren't we? Lots of little kids will be there.
I'm looking forward to it.
Isn't it early?
Isn't it early? Wait a minute.
We should all count down.
Countdown.
Are we ready?
Five seconds.
Five?
Seven, six, five!
Wait, what, what, what?
What do you mean?
Five seconds!
Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero!
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero!
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching!
thank you for watching!
Do you think you'll make it?
Do you think we'll make it?
What? Apple! Apple!
Buck!
Apple!
Thank you for watching.
You don't have to do anything you don't want to do.
I liked it. I liked it. I liked it.
I didn't want our hands to fall apart.
I don't want our hands to fall apart... if we get any closer.
I don't remember.
I'm chasing you... and in between...
I can't reach the part where you're holding me tight.
Can I wipe the sweat off my face?
Can I say that word?
When it's over
If you don't even notice
My on, my on, my on
I know this
I was in pain, I loved you
♪ Do you know if it's still going on ♪
Ah, always
Oh, my God!
Isn't this awesome?
Oh, my God.
That was the best fireworks ever.
The last one.
The last one was like a machine gun.
It was amazing!
Morisaki-san's heart was hard for 3 days, but in the blink of an eye
It was the end of the festival!
And so the Nakata Festival on November 3rd has begun!
Thank you very much!
Good afternoon
What are you asking me to do?
I don't know.
I see... thick barana juice.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
That's really great.
This is seriously amazing.
That was fun.
Please keep the calls to a minimum.
I'll do my best.
Yay!
Korea, how do you like Korea?
I was nervous, but Reiko Ueda really pulled me along like this, so I was able to do it easily.
She made me stand up first.
It was the most fun!
I'm so glad I came to the concert!
Three, two, one.
Fire!
Drummer.
Drawmer, I hope it's working for you all.
Thank you very much.
I'm very impressed.
It was a great event.
My feet are warm.
That's good.
To everyone at the event and to the audience
Thank you for a long time
See you again!
Seino
Bye-bye!
Which one?
Bye-bye
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.
Two days, I guess, for Google.
Thank you very much, really, for breaking down the platform so well,
Yes, I hope you all have a safe trip back.
New, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Let's take a picture with today's members.
Let's go, Chiyomi.
What are you doing?
All right, pictures.
Let's go with a sense of freedom, like we're done.
Three, two, one.
Open up more.
Open up.
Three, two, one.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for coming in today.
Everybody come in for a performer.
One more.
Thank you very much.
With the staff behind the scenes now.
Yes, sir.
It was all good in the end, wasn't it?
The fireworks were really great.
I could cry anytime.
And the food...
The interaction.
The music.
Fireworks.
There's usually a comedy stage.
Comedy live, sales, and so on.
You can see that kind of thing.
smiles that aren't comedy
that you usually see at comedy shows
That's what made me feel
I was really moved by that.
Everyone seemed so happy.
I thought it was great.
That's what I thought.
I thought you were doing this kind of event again.
Let's do it!
Let's do it.
Thank you very much. Please. It was my first time here and I had a great time.
I want to come again.
I want to come again. You said you enjoyed the beautiful fireworks. You say you're nervous? Don't be nervous.
I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back.
It was so beautiful.
Thank you for watching.